[music]
especially provided oh no on you
Switzerland her baby
weight you what is this shower to the question posts
Sochi thank you for your help
how
how to move forward 24 sugar cane
parrot action movies describes something in
you
when you look at something every time
you look at someone
you absolutely automatically spontaneously
think about I would like you to achieve
enlightenment
just there is such a small
grocery store someone
passes by we have to buy something and you
look at her say and
you would look good as if yes and
when this happens automatically I
can help you it seems to me yes you would
look good bowls those people whom you
don't know type
and it would suit you to be years old and this about
flashes in your head
when Pasha sugar bodhicitta
bodhicitta with our ego becomes
absolutely when you have such an
automatic desire to see a person
in some store or somewhere
refueling
or like
Joe and Joe and remember this place I
met him by the way recently
then you have absolute heach this
It's
good to know about this, and of course,
what if the option was with you, the teacher, and
which the base spoke, would tell you about
these little signs that you would
constantly apply and check, but which of
their bodhicitta is greater now, is this in theory
for me, or is it still the abahi of the
sugar cane chita, or sometimes I have a thought
somewhere at a gas station, maybe about a
flash of such a thought that I would like to see you, it would be
great to see you
enlightened, and
he says when you have such
random thoughts and there
will be other people here, then
you are approaching the absolute beekeepers
and
this is a sign that
you are very close along the
line to the first path,
follow about drinking
from the 5 levels of the spiritual path of each
person, people fall out,
no matter what religion you are in,
we are talking about the spiritual path,
you go through all these 5 levels of the
monastery, the paths of
spirituality, the idea of ​​awareness,
or are they synonyms in Buddhism,
the idea of ​​​​creating spiritual and we will find out,
and
also spiritual knowledge, they are all synonyms, the
five paths of the
state of understanding, and all people go
through 15 stages and
in their  life you go through these and
when you reach 1
by the way you naturally don't get there to
get to the first you will need a
lot of time and
what will be the sign that you are in the
first
[music] then this is some kind of
trouble in your life
when a big problem is called
renunciation when you are tired of your life and
when you are already tired of hoping that everything
will be okay this will be good
you were diagnosed with some
terrible disease cancer something is happening in
your life and you understand no it's not from
work
when you finally
achieve this renunciation you understand
that this is a dead end
someone told me
we were discussing the mortality rate and
people said life is mortal and and such
[music]
life can kill you
when you finally understand this
then in this glass of renunciation I remember I
asked my teacher a question
such a conversation in the kitchen you
need to have time to catch the teacher and every
time when I caught him at such a moment he got
irritated it was
necessary it was a kind of
talent to catch him I didn't serve
tea it's like well by the way teachers he is like
forward this tea is like
I am like the
difference
when we gain virtue  On the lower
tracks there are tracks and on the higher tracks and
when you get to Baja, reading you are
already on the path of accumulation, you have already reached 1
of 5 5
but further tracks you reach those
moments when you understand that life is
killing you, what is the connection, what is the connection
on the higher tracks on your path, it is the
same state of mind that this and this will also
kill me, but I did it for everyone, and
now my seagulls were falling, but I received
information from him in this way, I
learned the most from him, such moments,
such
moments of blackmail
when I served him
dumplings in, let's explain, don't deceive Mecca and
[music] and
so they
were reaching from the corner and
now you have
begun to accumulate good karma for the
next three billion years, you began
this process
on the day
when you had this feeling at the
gas station,
seeing someone
as a blood, any ordinary
person, random or it came to you
completely by chance, you
planned, you saw him and you thought it would be
great to bring them to enlightenment
when you have such awareness, that's when the countdown
begins, the countdown
which is divided by 3,
I just call it big  the figure of that
very, very long way
much longer than a
billion years and that's when the
countdown begins
we will have with you another parable story
from this moment when it began for him
from the moment when he
received the true kidnapping how much
time it took him
to achieve his goal this is approximately
this write 7 zeros approximately add and
so the countdown begins when you have this
experience
at the gas station you reach the corner
you have someone and the countdown began for you to
your enlightenment and
they say that no one can tell
you the exact time until you
reach Victor's patches cheats and will tell the
exact time when you achieve
wisdom
when when will his status even but and
I can tell this until you
have party chats but it is from this
moment that the countdown begins now everything is
according to plan now and on the schedule
why and our next picture the
train leaves and you talk to someone there
and
what is the connection here for 100 dollars
well
I want you to explain
try to write down dollars each
I just told you that we are here saying
goodbye to someone saying
goodbye to  someone who is on a train
or trying to get on this train for
100 dollars, why is
he
saying goodbye to someone, returning,
letting go of this train that is leaving,
rolling, developing his bodhichitta, and
here it appears, it appears in him,
and the countdown begins from this moment, he has
already come a long way and now he is
ready
to start again this carrot, this short
trip that will last about
three billion years,
he now hides the schedule according to plan, and on
this very day when you have a
spontaneous experience, maybe it will be
some cafe,
someone will come up, will go to the cafe, just an
ordinary person, and
think, I would do it, you will be, you
looked good, like, years, I should
bring you last, it seems, and that's when
this happens, your heart
automatically, you saw someone in a
coffee shop,
then we can call you, signed,
then you deserve this title, this
side, a lot
can happen, a lot can
happen at gas stations, first, you will meet a water pipe,
we went to this Mexican restaurant,
remember this, they had different
flavors, at the gas station, there were diamonds,
we can try this at the gas station, and it was
possible  I remember suddenly stealing something, a
mode came with me once and
then a
big guy with a gun appears and
they say, you know, Michael, they're filming a
movie there now,
I'm in a moment, this is all for real, this is a
real cowboy
movie, we have guys like that there
and on this very day you receive the
title, here's an hour, your
daughter will be victorious, well, or we're
talking with 0 victorious projectile or daughter
rose to the move and we have a
picture here for you,
these are two jobs and
maybe this is the kind of experience you have at the
gas station,
I finally joined this family,
I won't disgrace your family anymore,
I'm now a son, it's
so famous, these are famous
lines, if
you can use this construction,
trying to catch a plane at the
gas station and so you receive this title
for the first time, office from or you can say
now my name is I joined at 89, I
also belong to myself, it will be and
then
numerous wonderful things begin to happen,
some constant changes
[music]
I didn't know this word,
strange what, well, it happens that I
come across them too and he says if you add then
if you experience such experiences at the
gas station then
but I looked it up in the dictionary it
means
reinforcement for soldiers
as we say here the
cavalry appears reinforcement came at the
last moment it appeared as
reinforcement says tantric such
support when you experience such a
feeling for example back then it's like
rocket fuel you will definitely quickly
achieve visit
if you experience such feelings when
you see another person
[music]
and
without even planning
such a thought flashes through your mind that it would be
great to bring excitability then
tu turu tu tu
to the rescue antara runs exactly to set
and years
everything is already planned
nerve means peace does not mean very
quickly and one
hundred percent and so reinforcement came that's what
we have a picture here yes these are
tantric guys guys will become
this in order to shoot our
cliches our negative well done
our hearts and
further
and
he very briefly
talks about different types of bodhichitta there is a
classical classical division teaches and
which will help you deeply understand
how to get this
experience like for example at a gas station
there are
different about
30 types of different tramps we
will talk about some of them
if you divide it under birds then
its nature in different  You can divide it
into 2. Save the magic doesn't
mean
intention,
intention, motivation, helping other people.
You make decisions in your heart.
I would like to become such a being
that will help an infinite number of
other
beings. And this is something else. Video prayers and the
form of intentions and the
next type.
In fact, this is an action when you
begin to study the 6 types of perfections.
This is giving.
Hello, a way of life when we are not
angry, we
rejoice in when we do good
deeds, performs good deeds,
meditation and emptiness, understanding emptiness.
So we can divide it this way.
The first will flow. This is the
cape, such a desire, and the second is when
worse actions are practiced and
perfection is actually
doing something to serve others. People have been sledding for
years. It's very
interesting. We can divide these 4 this
way.
When we divide it based on
nature, this is when we have desire and
action, but we can also have 9 and other
ways.
As we call it,
levels of realization, levels of consciousness,
there is
experience, and the ketchup itself is CIS. This is interesting, but it's
very interesting how the separation occurs here.
What does it mean?
You are trying to become a bodhisattva.
I understand simply that, but your understanding
will arrive and at that moment.
This is the faith of your teachers. You hear
most of the teachers. They talk and
tell you about emptiness. You
like your teacher and you think
he's telling you the truth. This is called
inspiration. Inspiration by emptiness. It
seems like it sounds old. I
like how it sounds. Yes, I like this
and that. It seems to me that this probably sounds good.
The pen seems
great. This is
called chipa.
Your understanding of emptiness
is simply the faith of your teacher. Then
he copes with his understanding of emptiness.
This is called eternal
personal experience. If we compare this
with what the teacher tells you.
You try to do what the teacher says.
You listen to him. In
Odessa, this is Pasha. You have already confirmed to yourself that
you have already understood that emptiness
exists.
We studied this. 10
is called the king, similar
[music],
similar to the shepherd, and
sometimes good.
There is such a famous division into types.
Batchata
is people who eat this piece of
meat and they, that is, the intentions that they are the
first to reach, I receive the first in order to
inspire,
they say, follow me,
I'm going first, you do this.
Some kind of coat of arms is an
example.  The king serves and the king usually in
ancient times he started in front
now everything is happening the other way around politicians are
hiding somewhere behind and
sending others to
fight before everything was the other way around a king
or a king a region in front of his army and
this is called kings similar to hichet I
will get there first and you will follow me
then there is
[music] to
drive your herds go-go
I will meet meetings with you there
let's achieve I will lead become
Buddhas see you I will
hang out you
let's cross this line already and I will
follow you later I will be the last I
just want to make sure that everyone
gets there first and then I and
there is a
threshold cheek like
let's all together let's all go
wisdom at the same time
remember in Windows there are few bridges very
often small boats a small ferry
and they just transport you to the other
side of the river and and you are all in one 1 to the boat
and
here is such a philosophical problem a
thousand dollar question
no
so quiet quiet this is a lot of money
tried let's go in a circle again
let's change what half will get the
question was the following
what is the philosophical problem here what is the
problem here
so  Let me ask better, I'll get
complaints from you later, let's see
where you are first, let's try to
calm down, quietly,
Stanley was second
[music],
so they began to transmit to you, let's
slowly, slowly, and I will repeat,
and if you are right,
why is this problem,
you have practically earned 700 dollars,
I will ask you leading questions,
either everything, or everything, or nothing,
so such a proposal,
maybe we should really
wait,
and let you all achieve enlightenment, and
I
will delay my enlightenment,
maybe this is more, more love in
this beta version, as
I ask the question, she is wandering, you look like a
private house, in a show, in a shooting gallery,
in games,
my question is next,
what is more compassionate,
to stay in samsara until everyone gets out of
it, a
good question,
this is an expensive question,
when you stay in samsara,
you can stay there forever, maybe
you will get sucked in, will you like it and generally
forget about everything else,
of course, compassion, you want
people to achieve enlightenment with tags, but
then you have a chance to linger in this
samsara and not get enlightenment,
keep going, keep going,
that is,
I am on the right path and  Well,
all these divisions that we are now
talking about are like a cadastre, like a king, like
a lieutenant, like a shepherd, the
king says I will be the first to achieve
enlightenment, you do it like I do,
follow me, he will be an example for
others, the second he says,
you know, I will set fire to my enlightenment, I
will stay here, sasori, and you guys
are eating, cross this knowledge, and
actions are posts, say I do this
[music],
allow myself, and then I myself, after them, and
I will stay here, calm in the hall,
aka the very last of us will not cross
this line,
IS-3, the problem is
if you do not have the strength or the
opportunity to be the first to achieve enlightenment,
become enlightened, I will give you, I will give
you a thousand dollars, thank you,
this is a cool division, and
here there is
a small and precision,
this is the wrong idea when we remain
alone and wait for others to come to
dedicate the
most about when we, we do not
postpone our enlightenment for
a second, we go first in order to then
help others, this is wrong, the idea
seems to
sound very noble,
but this is the wrong example,
and Buda later says, yes, I was joking,
you are postponing for the sake of  someone no-no-no-don't
do in any case
eat this piece of meat yourself quickly
transfer cross this line and then
you will be able to help others it won't help if
you
make yourself a saint or a great martyr to
others so you won't help
yes we all want to develop ourselves like fleas
read kings will
[music]
no I definitely won't give you money for this
but 3 earned from 1000 then we
need to achieve enlightenment as quickly as possible
and then we
can really help people it's not like you
disappeared and
you
release samsara help people being in the hall
this is the question
I talked about this de plata
senior
monastery
older students they begin to
debate with new candidates and
he was from my college that's
behind his monastery and
I was a senior student and I
started a debate with him
right and I asked this question and
it's not the eye about which the stripe is the most
recent 15 is the master of debates dimension
let's allow tricks to participate
then just stops like
he decides for himself
when he does it usually someone has
problems
so that  Someone not to embarrass, he
stops him and
so we got a lasso and
continued the debate and we continued for about
2-3 hours on this very
issue
[music]
what kind of question
if
if you wait
will it be suffering for you to see
how other people suffer after their
enlightenment if you are the king
look back and you see how people
suffer how can you be a
king at the same time you will
no longer have seeds because this
suffering
I will give you half the amount
I will give you the 3rd option of and cook his
teacher I say cook say
think and
and
considering that
things are posts and will this not be a
contradiction and a
tantric being and see
see yourself as a suffering being both
correct his true
if what torments you is that things are posts
if the possibility that I will offend you as a
tantric being and you see yourself as a
suffering being
come on
[music]
I said something not quite alone scratch
but I will still see your suffering
how to line up and
then my paradise will be my
royo there will be problems before
think  Think,
reason,
I'll repeat now so that people also understand
what you're talking about.
We're talking now, couples,
then when we come to
enlightenment and we see everyone around us
enlightened, aren't
we
exactly the Great Race, people who achieve
enlightenment, do
we understand that everyone around us
suffers and
this is a very Vajrayana approach,
this is also a kind of proposal,
but this diamond must be
obtained in, you must first receive,
first against initiation,
but I winked at you,
something got in my eye,
by the way, there are no more
[music]
we say that many people are talking, it's
hard to hear, I apologize
if you stop, I'll be with you if
the signal to see what will be seen at this stage
if you have seeds to see yourself as if
breaking through,
you say,
but you're still describing vodka now,
I read your similar
in any case, I'll give it anyway, these are your
seeds that you press, that this is your shift,
that is, do you see yourself as a king or
as a park cheek,
this is logical,
tantra is built on this, it's not something that
small, the very idea of ​​the center is built on
it
quite deeply
everyone has cleared out my pockets it becomes an
expensive pleasure
so we talked about three types there is one more
way of
dividing
there is a very famous endowment of
2222 lead
I once talked about this taught this in
my opinion with such I
in exchange for pizza feeling
such a decision was made that we will
study at the walls from 8 to 3 in the morning and
so there is also it would be
great to know all these differences
sometimes she is on the course of cash
we
if it is difficult to understand these divisions
3222 yes this is a metaphor
it is like the sun or the ocean or
just they are not so beautiful
will be a good topic
[music] a
very good topic for uncle groups of
students I and the groups
can make out all these beats
if the doors are Nivea Peacocks then now
let's try to do it will be great
good
when it is with us on Tuesday Thursday
how can we make an upgrade
yes by the way the volunteers who
work here they are all by definition yes by the way it
will be great and let's do
why for
how long will we have two hours
until 40 managed
well and
he says listen to Pamukkale almost in
classes he says we have
finished the seven steps of reasons naturally
and  When we start and we ourselves have equal equal
treatment,
you know that everyone was yours in the material and I
want to repay her kindness in kind, I
want to take away your problems and make you
happy, and I will do it myself, and as a
result, we are already talking about distinguishing, and
he says we have gone through it with you, we will go
family step by step, what is next,
yes, let's analyze the shanti system,
let's
take these two methods when there is a
joyful attitude and exchanging yourself for
others,
here they sometimes translate incorrectly, the
first one, I will try to learn to treat
everyone differently, and the second one is I
will try to practice, take, apply the
practice, one of the others, sometimes it is incorrect
to confuse, and
I have a picture for you here,
we used it somehow else, and
this is a
step-by-step process of two steps, so
first, I say this myself, this is a different joyful
relationship,
you can emphasize openly say equal rights
for happiness for everyone, there is
no such thing as someone not deserving
to be happy, we all have different
equal rights to be happy in  We
all have ranks, the right to
happiness, and
now I'm
getting a little ahead of myself.
We all also have equal rights to avoid
pain.
When we say that we have different rights
to happiness, we also all have equal rights
not to suffer. The
second part is
blaming others. This isn't just
when it sounds. It's not
just when it sounds. It's not
like you just walked for 9
hours and almost the means are deeper,
or we'll get to that.
Then he says something very interesting.
I
admit
that you can use this
seven-step process and you will achieve bodhichitta. But
if you want to charge your seven steps,
I offer you a
masterpiece. You can achieve it
using a step-by-step plan. But if you
want super baking, I suggest you
try this system. The
masters that they give you.
He says that somehow,
if you are going to destroy the razor,
add more and the system. All together,
it's much more powerful.
Shevchik means very strong, super
powerful.
So,
let's move on to the master. Now, I'm
running out of time, and
so we rest.
Where do you want to go, by
the way?  We'll do this tomorrow,
so we have 10 minutes here in nature,
then we'll have,
but don't worry, and we'll go back to the
master to sew for
those in Asia and see life, well, come up with a
good question.